

Contact me@manuelbussmann.com 079 942 68 29

dribbble.com/Manuel B behance.net/manuelbussmann

6130 Willisau

linkedin.com/in/manuelbussmann/

Tools

Figma

Sketch

Adobe XD

InDesign

Illustrator

Photoshop

Wordpress

Webflow

Skills

UX Research

Sketching

Wireframing

Design Thinking

typography

UI Design

Prototyping

HTML CSS

Image enhancement

Languages

German Native language

English Level C1

Manuel Bussmann

UI & UX DESIGNER

For two years now, I have been investing most of my time and money in project-based design training. This allows me to continually improve my ability to create user-centric design solutions that are simple, aesthetically pleasing and pixel perfect.

My logistical background helps me to work in an organized way and to save my files systematically.

Education

UI CERTIFICATION

Careerfoundry | 03-2019 - ongoing

- Implementation of Ux Research, User Interviews, Preference Testing
- Design and branding of a banking app, online store and cooking app
- Creation of sketches, low & high fidelity wireframes, app prototypes

Work Experience

MEDIAMATIC APPRENTICESHIP

7s Medical AG | 07-2018 - Ongoing

- Design of the three portfolio catalogs in interactive design
- Creation of all visual content for flyers and catalogs
- Product photography and photo editing
- Optimization of the online store & cutting the loading time in half
- Responsible for all print marketing material

POST LOGISTIC

Post Swiss AG | 04-2018 - 07-2018

LANGUAGE STAY

Easy SL Malta | 09-2017 - 03-2018

LOGISTICIAN EFZ

INTERIO (MVN) | 08-2014 — 07-2017